(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(테마 음악 재생)
FAMILY: THE UNBREAKABLE BOND
가족: 깨지지 않는 유대
(GROANS)
(신음소리)
(SOFT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(부드럽고 재미있는 음악 재생)
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(LAUGHING)
(웃음)
(GRUNTING RHYTHMICALLY)
(리듬적으로 투덜거림)
This is crazy.
이건 미친 짓이야.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
One more time.
한 번 더.
(CHUCKLES)
(웃음)
-(CELL PHONE VIBRATES) -So sexy.
-(휴대폰이 진동함) -너무 섹시해요.
Yura must be so happy.
유라가 정말 행복할 것 같아요.
No Minseo tonight.
오늘 밤에는 민서가 없어요.
Hurry up, honey.
서둘러요, 자기야.
I'm on my way. I think I'll be home early.
지금 가는 중이에요. 집에 일찍 들어갈 것 같아요.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(깊은 한숨)
Oh! This is crazy.
아! 이건 미친 짓이야.
I forgot my ring. (CHUCKLES)
반지를 잊어버렸어요. (웃음)
(CLICKS TONGUE, CHUCKLES)
(혀를 찰칵, 낄낄거림)
Whoa!
와!
(CHUCKLING)
(낄낄거림)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(깊은 한숨)
(GRUNTS)
(끙끙거림)
(LAUGHING)
(웃음)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
(초인종이 울림)
Be right there.
바로 거기에 있어.
(VOCALIZING)
(발성)
(EXCLAIMS HAPPILY)
(행복하게 외친다)
(LAUGHS)
(웃음)
Chief Oh. What are you doing here?
오 과장. 여기서 뭐하는거야?
I have something to say.
할 말이 있어요.
Did you call your wife?
아내에게 전화했어요?
I have no time. I've got so much to do.
시간이 없어요. 할 일이 너무 많아요.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
-I'm in a rush too. -Hey.
-나도 바빠요. -여기요.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYS)
(테마 음악 재생)
FAMILY: THE UNBREAKABLE BOND
가족: 깨지지 않는 유대
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
(부드럽게 한숨을 쉬다)
Episode 3
에피소드 3
He's leaving in 3 days. Finish it before then.
그는 3일 후에 떠날 예정이다. 그 전에 끝내세요.
If it's urgent, give it to Jaeyeol.
급하면 재열이한테 주세요.
And I can't go over it in 3 days.
그리고 3일 안에는 끝낼 수 없어요.
Chief Oh.
오 과장.
Let's respect each other's way of work.
서로의 일하는 방식을 존중합시다.
All right? Here.
괜찮은? 여기.
Jaeyeol and I are going on a business trip to Incheon tomorrow.
재열이랑 나랑 계속 내일 인천 출장.
This guy trafficked over 300 children abroad.
이 사람은 인신매매됐어요 해외에 300명 이상의 어린이가 있습니다.
Mostly for sexual exploitation and organ harvesting.
주로 성착취용 그리고 장기 적출.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
What's there to double-check?
다시 확인할 사항은 무엇입니까?
(SIGHS) This is crazy.
(한숨) 이건 미친 짓이야.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(LOW SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(낮은 긴장감 있는 음악 재생)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
(도어 잠금 해제)
DOHOON: Go now.
도훈: 이제 가세요.
CHIEF OH: I said there's no time. Don't double-check.
오 수석: 시간이 없다고 했어요. 다시 확인하지 마세요.
DOHOON: I just did. I'll get to it tomorrow.
도훈: 그냥 그랬어요. 내일부터 알아보겠습니다.
I can start from tomorrow.
내일부터 시작할 수 있어요.
CHIEF OH: You better hurry up.
OH 최고: 서두르는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
DOHOON: What's so urgent? You need to leave now.
도훈: 뭐가 그렇게 급해요? 지금 떠나야 해요.
My wife will be here in any minute. Now, leave.
제 아내가 곧 여기에 올 거예요. 이제 떠나세요.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(부드럽게 헐떡거린다)
Honey.
여보.
Oh!
오!
This isn't what you think it is.
이것은 당신이 생각하는 것이 아닙니다.
No.
아니요.
That's never true.
그것은 결코 사실이 아닙니다.
(CHUCKLING) That's not it.
(웃음) 그건 아니고요.
Chief Oh, say something.
아, 팀장님, 말씀 좀 해주세요.
Tell her.
그녀에게 말하세요.
Oh. She's taking it the wrong way.
오. 그녀는 그것을 잘못된 방향으로 받아들이고 있습니다.
Say something.
말해보세요.
Let's grab a drink.
한잔 마시자.
DOHOON: Why would you grab a drink with her?
도훈: 왜 그러는데? 그 사람이랑 한잔 할래?
Drink here.
여기서 마셔보세요.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(감동적인 음악이 계속됩니다)
CHIEF OH: This is taking forever.
OH 최고: 시간이 오래 걸리네요.
YURA: Did you sleep together?
유라: 같이 잤어요?
Or was it their first time?
아니면 처음이었나요?
No, it didn't look like it.
아니요, 그렇지 않은 것 같았습니다.
CHIEF OH: Why doesn't she talk, I'm right here!
오 사장: 왜 말을 안 해요? 나는 바로 여기 있다!
YURA: Since when? This year? Last year?
유라: 언제부터요? 올해? 작년?
Or even before we got married?
아니면 결혼하기 전에도요?
CHIEF OH: Just ask. I'll give you the answer you want.
오 수석: 그냥 물어보세요. 원하시는 답변을 드리겠습니다.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(감동적인 음악이 계속됩니다)
(GAGS)
(개그)
(EXHALES)
(숨을 내쉬다)
Hey.
안녕.
When are you going to stop drinking?
언제쯤 술을 끊을 예정인가요?
You didn't call me for drinks.
당신은 나에게 술 한잔 하려고 전화한 게 아니었습니다.
Just say whatever's on your mind.
그냥 생각나는 대로 말하세요.
Right. Dohoon--
오른쪽. 도훈--
Damn it.
젠장.
(GLASS THUDS)
(유리 쿵)
(EXCLAIMS ANGRILY)
(화가 나서 소리친다)
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(부드럽게 낄낄거린다)
Right. It's better this way.
그렇죠. 이 방법이 더 좋습니다.
Better. (CHUCKLING)
더 나은. (CHUCKLING)
I got water in my ear.
귀에 물이 들었어요.
-(DRINK POURING) -(SIGHS)
-(술을 붓는다) -(한숨)
(EXHALES)
(숨을 내쉬다)
Take him.
그를 데려가세요.
Take what?
무엇을 가져갈까요?
Go ahead, take Dohoon.
어서 도훈을 데려가세요.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(낭만적인 음악 재생)
(CHUCKLING)
(낄낄거림)
(LAUGHING)
(웃음)
(HIGH-PITCHED LAUGHING)
(큰 웃음소리)
But I can't give up everything.
하지만 모든 것을 포기할 수는 없습니다.
You can't give up what?
포기할 수 없는 게 뭐야?
I can't give up my family.
나는 가족을 포기할 수 없습니다.
Just take only him.
그 사람만 데려가세요.
(LOW PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(낮고 재미있는 음악 재생)
-(GLASS THUDS) -(DRINK POURING)
-(유리 쿵) -(술을 붓는다)
So, what's it going to be?
그럼 어떻게 될까요?
Dohoon's pretty good.
도훈이는 좀 괜찮아요.
But he's always too hasty. He's not my type.
하지만 그 사람은 늘 너무 성급해요. 그 사람은 내 타입이 아니야.
I'll just borrow him from time to time like now.
그냥 가끔 빌려줄게 지금처럼.
Borrow him?
그를 빌려?
Isn't it better for you to lend him
그 사람에게 빌려주는 것이 낫지 않나요?
rather than giving him away?
그를 포기하는 것보다?
If I borrow him officially,
내가 그를 공식적으로 빌리면,
does he come with warranty?
그 사람 보증도 같이 오나요?
Warranty, my foot.
보증, 내 발.
Why would I do that?
내가 왜 그럴까요?
(LOUDLY) Fix him yourself!
(큰 소리로) 그 사람을 직접 고치세요!
What are you saying?
무슨 말을 하는 거야?
(LAUGHING)
(웃음)
What are you doing?
뭐하는 거야?
You thought I was having an affair with him.
넌 내가 바람피운다고 생각했지? 그와 함께.
I was just playing along.
난 그냥 같이 놀고 있었어.
Did you fall for it?
그것에 빠졌나요?
Fall for what?
무엇에 빠지나요?
You totally fell for it.
당신은 그것에 완전히 빠졌습니다.
You totally did. I can see it in your eyes.
정말 그랬어요. 나는 당신의 눈에서 그것을 볼 수 있습니다.
My goodness. Maybe I should become an actress.
이럴 수가. 어쩌면 나는 배우가 되어야 할지도 모른다.
(LAUGHING)
(웃음)
I totally got you.
나는 당신을 완전히 이해했습니다.
So there's nothing between you two. You...
그러니까 너희 둘 사이에는 아무 일도 없어. 당신은...
expect me to believe that?
내가 그 말을 믿을 거라고 기대하시나요?
Dohoon
도훈
is my colleague as well as a partner for over 10 years.
내 동료야 10년 넘게 파트너이기도 합니다.
I give him an assignment, he does it better than anyone.
나는 그에게 임무를 주는데, 그는 누구보다 그 일을 더 잘한다.
So I value him.
그래서 나는 그를 소중히 여깁니다.
That's all.
그게 다야.
Whether you believe it or not
당신이 믿든 안 믿든
is none of my business.
내 일이 아니야.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(심호흡)
(DRINK POURING)
(음료를 붓는다)
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(SNIFFLES) I...
(훌쩍 웃으며) 나...
I never liked you since the moment I first met you.
난 당신을 좋아한 적이 없어요 당신을 처음 만난 순간부터.
Why are you trying to buy my family with money?
왜 우리 가족을 사려고 합니까? 돈으로?
You think money is everything?
돈이 전부라고 생각하시나요?
Is everything expensive good?
비싼 건 다 좋은 걸까?
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
My father-in-law has orthostatic hypotension.
나의 시아버지는 기립성 저혈압.
He fell while hiking
그는 하이킹을 하다가 넘어졌다
because he suddenly felt dizzy,
갑자기 어지러움을 느꼈기 때문이다.
and you're getting him on a plane?
그런데 그 사람을 비행기에 태워줄 건가요?
Orthostatic hypotension? That's dangerous.
기립성 저혈압? 그건 위험해요.
What's more important is,
더 중요한 것은,
when my mother-in-law passed away,
시어머니가 돌아가셨을 때,
she gave me a mission
그녀는 나에게 임무를 주었다
to stop him from seeing anyone.
그가 누구와도 만나지 못하도록.
I worked so hard to stop him
나는 그를 막기 위해 너무 열심히 일했습니다
from seeing anyone in secret.
누군가를 비밀리에 보지 못하도록.
If he goes to Qingdao with Ms. Park,
만약 그가 박씨와 함께 칭다오에 간다면,
how am I going to face my mother-in-law later?
나는 어떻게 직면할 것인가 나중에 시어머니?
Oh, I wasn't aware
아 몰랐네요
of all the complicated story between this and the underworld.
그 모든 복잡한 이야기들 사이에서 이것과 지하세계.
"She looked really cute when she received the award."
"정말 귀엽게 생겼어. 상 받았을 때."
"She was sad no one from her family was coming,
"그녀는 슬펐어요 그녀의 가족 중 누구도 오지 않았고,
"so I went instead." Why would you go instead?
"그래서 내가 대신 갔어." 왜 대신 가겠습니까?
Why couldn't I make it?
왜 나는 그것을 할 수 없었습니까?
Because of you!
당신 때문에!
Yura, about that... (CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
유라, 그거... (어색하게 웃는다)
When I went there,
내가 거기 갔을 때,
it wasn't anything fancy like you think.
당신이 생각하는 것만큼 멋진 일은 아니었어요.
If you really want to go, you can go
정말 가고 싶으면 가도 돼요
when she gets awarded again next time.
다음에 또 상을 받을 때요.
Who says she can get awarded again?
그녀가 다시 상을 받을 수 있다고 누가 말하던가요?
This is almost like a miracle.
이것은 거의 기적과 같습니다.
You shook her mother off on the day
넌 그날 그 애 엄마를 흔들어 놨어
that could've been the first and last day in her life!
그게 처음이었을 수도 있어 그리고 그녀 인생의 마지막 날!
Right, I'm sorry.
그렇죠, 죄송합니다.
It's my bad.
그건 내 잘못이야.
Let's drink and shake it off.
마시고 털어내자.
Let's drink some more.
좀 더 마시자.
-Whatever. -Here. Drink.
-무엇이든. -여기. 마시다.
-(DRINK POURING) -(CHIEF OH EXCLAIMS)
-(술을 붓는다) -(오 과장님이 외친다)
Forget it.
잊어버리세요.
I don't drink with people I don't like.
나는 싫어하는 사람과는 술을 마시지 않는다.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(감동적인 음악 재생)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(깊은 한숨)
CHIEF OH: All men are the same.
오 수석: 남자는 다 똑같다.
They're damn selfish
존나 이기적인 놈들이네
and damn disloyal.
그리고 빌어먹을 불충성한.
They never show even a tiny bit of comradeship to their wives.
그들은 조금도 보여주지 않아 of comradeship to their wives.
You said your first ex-husband, Byunggil,
첫 전남편이라고 하셨죠. 병길님,
was the most disloyal.
was the most disloyal.
What?
무엇?
How do you know Byunggil?
How do you know Byunggil?
Your first ex Ko Byunggil.
첫 전 남친 고병길.
Second ex Heo Seungtae. Third ex Im Jaewon.
Second ex Heo Seungtae. 세 번째 전 임재원.
Oh, right.
아, 그렇죠.
I told you all about my divorce stories. (LAUGHING)
제가 이혼 이야기를 다 말했어요. (웃음)
One more bottle please.
한 병 더 주세요.
(SIGHS)
(SIGHS)
I'm lonely.
나는 외롭다.
I'm so lonely.
I'm so lonely.
No parents. No husband.
부모가 없습니다. No husband.
I pity you.
안타깝습니다.
Right? I'm pitiful, aren't I?
오른쪽? I'm pitiful, aren't I?
Since I look beautiful like a celeb,
연예인처럼 예뻐서
everyone thinks my life is sweet.
모두들 내 인생이 달콤하다고 생각해요.
But that's never the case.
그러나 결코 그렇지 않습니다.
Seriously, I am
진심으로, 나는
darn pitiful.
정말 불쌍하다.
(SIGHS) Thank you for recognizing it.
(한숨) 알아봐주셔서 감사해요.
Pity, my butt. Why am I listening to this?
불쌍하다, 내 엉덩이. 내가 이 말을 왜 듣고 있는 걸까?
(EXHALES)
(숨을 내쉬다)
Huh? Hey, where are you going?
뭐? 이봐, 어디 가는 거야?
-Hey. -The restroom.
-여기요. -화장실.
Hurry up.
서둘러요.
(LINE RINGING)
(라인 벨 울림)
CHIEF OH
오 과장
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(깊은 한숨)
She's never picking up.
그녀는 결코 전화를받지 않습니다.
By now,
지금쯤이면,
she should've picked up once by mistake.
그녀는 실수로 한 번 전화를 받았어야 했어요.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
AUTOMATED VOICE: The number you have reached...
자동 음성: 당신이 도달한 숫자는...
CHIEF OH
오 과장
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(LINE RINGING)
(라인 벨 울림)
CHIEF OH: (DRUNKENLY) Why? Why!
오과장: (술에 취해) 왜요? 왜!
"Why?"
"왜?"
What are you two doing?
둘이서 뭐해요?
Since when were you so close? You have that much to talk about?
언제부터 그렇게 친했어? 할 얘기가 그렇게 많나요?
Chief Oh. Listen to me.
오 과장. 내 말을 들어보세요.
I can't take this anymore!
나는 이것을 더 이상 참을 수 없다!
Hey.
여기요.
You better be nice to Yura.
유라에게 잘 대해주는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
All she talks about is you.
그녀가 말하는 것은 당신뿐입니다.
It's all about you.
그것은 모두 당신에 관한 것입니다.
My ears are going to bleed.
귀에서 피가 날 것 같아요.
What a great couple.
정말 멋진 커플이에요.
You're just meant to be together.
당신은 단지 함께 있기로되어 있습니다.
So darn loud.
너무 시끄러워요.
Calm down now.
이제 진정하세요.
Come and get your wife.
와서 아내를 데려오세요.
Now!
지금!
-(LINE DISCONNECTS) -(HICCUPS, CLEARS THROAT)
-(라인 연결 끊김) -(딸꾹질, 목이 가빠진다)
Oh, oh, oh!
아, 아, 아!
Seriously.
진지하게.
How can you drink until you pass out?
기절할 때까지 어떻게 술을 마실 수 있나요?
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(소프트 음악 재생)
(SMACKS LIPS)
(입술을 톡톡 친다)
Good.
좋아요.
Done.
완료.
(SLOW SONG PLAYING IN ENGLISH) Shall we dance?
(영어로 느린 노래 재생) 우리 춤춰볼까?
And shall we love?
그리고 우리 사랑할까요?
I know you hate me, mm-hmm...
당신이 나를 싫어한다는 걸 알아요, 음-흠...
(IN KOREAN) Minseo, are you ready?
(IN KOREAN) 민서야 준비됐어?
MINSEO: Boseok, what are you doing?
민서: 보석 씨, 뭐 해요?
Where are you? Do you want to go to school together?
어디세요? 같이 학교에 갈래?
Want me to come over to your house?
내가 당신 집에 가길 바라나요?
(SONG CONTINUES IN ENGLISH) ...is yours until the sun goes down
(노래는 영어로 계속됩니다) ...해가 질 때까지 당신의 것입니다
So, let's drink strawberry wine...
그럼 딸기 와인을 마시자...
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(IN KOREAN) Let's make fried eggs.
(IN KOREAN) 계란후라이를 만들어 볼까요.
(SIZZLING)
(지글지글)
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
(노래가 불분명하게 계속 재생됨)
Minseo.
민서.
Are you listening?
듣고 있나요?
(SONG CONTINUES IN ENGLISH) And I'll wake you just in time
(노래는 영어로 계속됩니다) 그리고 딱 맞춰서 널 깨워줄게
To go missing a hundred miles
100마일을 놓치기 위해
Till we run out of time...
시간이 다 될 때까지...
(IN KOREAN) Why isn't he replying?
(IN KOREAN) 그 사람은 왜 답장이 없나요?
(GASPS) Is there no signal in the restroom?
(GASPS) 신호가 없나요 화장실에서?
(SPITS)
(침)
Let's wash your hair.
머리를 감아보자.
I didn't even wash my face, why wash my hair first?
얼굴도 안씻었는데 왜 머리를 먼저 감아?
Boseok won't like a stinky woman.
보석은 냄새나는 여자를 좋아하지 않을 것이다.
Good girl.
좋은 여자.
(WATER RUNNING)
(물 달리기)
TODAY IS NOT YOUR OVULATION PERIOD
오늘은 배란일이 아닙니다.
(DOOR OPENS)
(문이 열린다)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(문이 닫힘)
Minseo. Get ready quickly and come down.
민서. Get ready quickly and come down.
Hmm?
흠?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(문이 닫힘)
What? You have something to say?
무엇? 할 말 있어?
No.
아니요.
Where did I put it?
내가 그것을 어디에 두었나요?
I'm sure I put it here somewhere.
분명 여기 어딘가에 놓아두었을 거에요.
Excuse me. Sorry.
실례합니다. 죄송합니다.
(GRUNTING)
(끙끙거림)
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
죄송합니다. 괜찮으세요?
Last night,
어젯밤,
what did you say to Chief Oh?
오과장님한테 뭐라고 했어요?
Oh, well... It's just...
아, 뭐... 그건 그냥...
-MINSEO: Mom! Dad! -What?
-MINSEO: Mom! 아빠! -무엇?
What's wrong? What is it?
무슨 일이야? 그것은 무엇입니까?
-What's wrong? -What?
- 무슨 일이야? -무엇?
Oh, my gosh. Boseok replied!
아, 이런. Boseok replied!
He went to school early for the play practice.
그는 일찍 학교에 갔다 연극 연습을 위해.
-You scared me big time. -(SIGHS) You really scared me.
-당신은 나에게 큰 겁을 줬어요. -(한숨) 당신 정말 무서웠어요.
I want to go to school now.
I want to go to school now.
Dad, take me to school now.
아빠, 지금 저를 학교에 데려다 주세요.
Have breakfast before you go.
가기 전에 아침 식사를 하세요.
I don't care about breakfast.
I don't care about breakfast.
Dad, hurry.
아빠, 서둘러요.
Did you make a promise?
약속했어요?
We pretty much did.
우리는 거의 그랬습니다.
Look.
바라보다.
Boseok, where are you?
Boseok, where are you?
Do you want to go to school together? Want me to come over to your house?
Do you want to go to school together? Want me to come over to your house?
BOSEOK: School. Play practice.
보석: 학교요. 연습을 하세요.
See? I told you.
보다? 내가 말했잖아.
Why's he replying like that?
Why's he replying like that?
School. School. School. School.
학교. 학교. 학교. 학교.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Boseok's blood type is O.
보석의 혈액형은 O형입니다.
He can give his blood to anyone.
He can give his blood to anyone.
Isn't that amazing?
정말 놀랍지 않나요?
Really?
정말?
My blood type is also O.
제 혈액형도 O형이에요.
I can give my blood to everyone as much as I want. Glug, glug, glug.
내 피를 모두에게 줄 수 있어요 as much as I want. 글루그, 글루그, 글루그.
Isn't Daddy amazing?
아빠 정말 대단하지 않나요?
No.
아니요.
Boseok can even whistle.
보석은 휘파람도 불 수 있다.
It's really cool.
정말 멋지다.
No. I can even rap by whistling.
아니요. 휘파람으로 랩도 할 수 있어요.
Want to see?
보고 싶나요?
(BEATBOXING)
(BEATBOXING)
(CHUCKLING)
(낄낄거림)
Isn't Daddy really cool?
Isn't Daddy really cool?
Awesome, right?
정말 멋지죠?
No.
아니요.
Boseok can...
보석이는...
He...
He...
What about Boseok? What about him?
보석은 어때요? 그 사람은 어때요?
Oh, his name is Boseok.
아, 그 사람 이름은 보석이에요.
Even his name shines.
그의 이름조차 빛난다.
Really?
정말?
Daddy's name is...
Daddy's name is...
I paid one million won for it.
I paid one million won for it.
It's a very expensive name.
참 비싼 이름이군요.
Minseo. Eat this.
민서. 이것을 먹어라.
I don't like apple jam--
나는 사과잼을 좋아하지 않는다.
Too bad. Don't be so picky. That's a bad girl.
안타깝네요. 너무 까다롭게 굴지 마세요. That's a bad girl.
Eat.
먹다.
Hurry. You have to finish it.
서두르다. 끝내야합니다.
If you don't, I'm telling Mom.
안 그러면 엄마한테 말할 거야.
We're here.
우리는 여기에 있습니다.
Minseo, say bye before you go.
민서야, 가기 전에 인사 좀 해라.
Whose son did that to my daughter?
누구 아들이 내 딸에게 그런 짓을 했나요?
Boseok. I'm not going to say anything bad to your parents.
보석. 나는 말하지 않을 것이다 부모님한테 나쁜 짓이라도 하세요.
I just want to tell them you're a smart student
난 그냥 그들에게 말하고 싶어 당신은 똑똑한 학생이에요
and that you listen to your teachers.
그리고 선생님의 말씀을 듣는 것입니다.
I just want to compliment you.
나는 단지 당신을 칭찬하고 싶습니다.
I don't need a compliment.
나는 칭찬이 필요하지 않습니다.
Still, I need to talk to them.
그래도 난 그들과 얘기를 해야 해요.
That's my duty.
그게 내 의무예요.
Boseok.
보석.
Minseo. Hi.
민서. 안녕.
Mr. Song.
송 씨.
Hello.
안녕하세요.
Tell your parents, okay?
부모님한테 말해, 알았지?
They need to come to school by this week.
그 사람들은 학교에 와야 해 이번 주까지.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(문이 닫힘)
Boseok, let's practice together.
보석아, 같이 연습하자.
I'm done. Practice by yourself.
난 끝났어. 스스로 연습하세요.
MINSEO: What?
민서: 뭐?
Why does Mr. Song want to see his parents?
송씨는 왜? 그 사람 부모님을 보고 싶어?
Mr. Song.
송 씨.
Why did you tell Boseok to bring his parents?
왜 보석한테 말했어? 그의 부모님을 데려오려고?
What did Boseok do so wrong?
보석이가 무슨 잘못을 한 걸까요?
Minseo, it's not just his parents.
민서야, 그 사람 부모님만 그런 게 아니야.
Your parents came last month too.
너희 부모님도 지난달에 오셨어.
My mom yelled at me that night.
그날 밤 엄마는 나에게 소리를 질렀다.
You told on me.
You told on me.
STUDENTS: She's right.
학생: 그녀 말이 맞아요.
-She's right. -That was mean.
- 그 사람 말이 맞아요. -그건 심했어.
Be quiet.
조용히 하세요.
It's true.
사실이에요.
Told on you? A teacher would never do that, Minseo.
너한테 말했어? 선생님은 절대 그런 짓 안 해, 민서.
MINSEO: Sion.
민서: 시온.
Your dad yelled at you
네 아버지가 너한테 소리를 지르셨어
for calling the principal a bald vulture, right?
교장 선생님께 전화해서 대머리 독수리죠?
Yes. He yelled at me because Mr. Song told him.
예. 그는 나에게 소리를 질렀다 송 선생님이 그에게 말씀하셨거든요.
Songyi.
송이.
He told your parents you got two on your test, didn't he?
그 사람이 네 부모님께 너 두 개 갖고 있다고 말했잖아 네 시험에서 그랬지, 그렇지?
Yes. I told them I got 50,
예. 나는 그들에게 50개를 얻었다고 말했고,
but I got caught because of him.
그런데 그 사람 때문에 잡혔어요.
(STUDENTS COMPLAINING)
(학생들의 불평)
-Yes, me too. -I got in trouble because of you.
-네, 저도요. -너 때문에 곤란해졌어.
Quiet!
조용한!
Minseo, that's not true.
민서야, 그건 사실이 아니야.
If you're going to call Boseok's parents
보석 부모님한테 전화할 거면
and get him in trouble like us,
그 사람도 우리처럼 곤경에 빠지게 만들면
don't call them.
그들에게 전화하지 마세요.
-Don't call them. -She's right.
- 그 사람들한테 전화하지 마세요. - 그 사람 말이 맞아요.
RESTROOM
화장실
(STUDENTS COMPLAINING IN DISTANCE)
(멀리서 불평하는 학생들)
(LOUDLY) Quiet!
(큰 소리로) 조용히 해!
Minseo, that's never true!
민서야, 그건 절대 사실이 아니야!
MINSEO: Boseok is very kind, smart,
민서: 보석이는 정말 친절하고, 똑똑하고,
cool and nice to his friends.
그의 친구들에게 쿨하고 친절하다.
-Yes.
-예.
MINSEO: Boseok is very kind.
민서: 보석이는 정말 친절해요.
He lent me money.
그는 나에게 돈을 빌려주었습니다.
Don't call his parents!
그의 부모님께 전화하지 마세요!
-Don't. -Don't call them.
-하지 않다. - 그 사람들한테 전화하지 마세요.
Don't call his parents.
그의 부모님께 전화하지 마세요.
(STUDENTS AGREEING)
(학생들의 동의)
-Don't. -Don't call them.
-하지 마세요. - 그 사람들한테 전화하지 마세요.
Mr. Song.
송 씨.
What's going on?
무슨 일이야?
Mr. Principal.
교장선생님.
Guys. Say hello to the principal.
얘들아. 교장 선생님께 인사드립니다.
Okay. I get it.
좋아요. 알겠습니다.
I won't call them.
나는 그들에게 전화하지 않을 것입니다.
I won't call Boseok's parents.
보석 부모님한테는 전화 안 할 거예요.
CHIEF OH: MGD Union is known to have broken up due to their internal conflict
오 수석: MGD 유니온은 내부 갈등으로 인해 헤어진
in the 2000s.
2000년대에.
But the investigation shows
하지만 조사 결과에 따르면
they reassembled in Vladivostok.
그들은 블라디보스토크에서 재집결했습니다.
MAN: (ON CALL) Any infiltration in Korea?
남자: (통화 중) 한국에 침투한 적 있나요?
CHIEF OH: We investigated that they're behind
오 실장: 우리가 그걸 조사했어요. 그들은 뒤에 있어요
the spread of cocaine trafficking in Thailand.
코카인 밀매의 확산 태국에서.
They're also behind arms smuggling
그들도 무기 밀수를 하고 있어요
that connects Russia, Korea and the Philippines
러시아를 연결하는 한국과 필리핀
and it needs to be handled immediately.
즉시 처리해야 합니다.
After searching the disguised delivery man Min Junki's house,
위장 검색 후 배달원 민준기 집,
we've found the key figure of the Union
우리는 연합의 핵심 인물을 찾았습니다
is smuggling through Incheon Port tomorrow.
밀수입이다 내일 인천항을 통해.
So we're currently waiting at the port.
그래서 우리는 현재 항구에서 기다리고 있습니다.
The key figure?
핵심 인물은?
Aside from his nickname Dominic,
그의 별명 도미닉 외에도
his age, gender and nationality are all unidentified.
그의 나이, 성별, 국적 모두 신원이 밝혀지지 않았습니다.
We're currently working on his reason for entry.
우리는 현재 일하고 있습니다 그의 입국 이유에 대해.
We're going to check the domestic connection route and handle it.
국내를 확인해보겠습니다 연결 경로를 확인하고 처리합니다.
If we miss it, it's going to be a pain in the neck.
놓치면, 목이 아플 것입니다.
Be prepared thoroughly. And report real-time.
철저하게 준비하세요. 그리고 실시간으로 보고하세요.
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
(CALL DISCONNECTS)
(통화가 끊김)
Report if you've started.
시작했다면 신고하세요.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(감동적인 음악 재생)
(EXHALES)
(숨을 내쉬다)
(DISTANT SHIP HORNS BLOWING)
(DISTANT SHIP HORNS BLOWING)
This is the smuggling route Min Junki used.
This is the smuggling route Min Junki used.
According to our information,
According to our information,
Dominic will arrive here today or tomorrow.
도미니크가 여기 도착할 거예요 오늘 아니면 내일.
It's the restored data on Min Junki's phone.
복원된 데이터입니다 민준기 휴대폰으로.
Why would Min Junki meet Carly Young...
Why would Min Junki meet Carly Young...
-(CELL PHONE BEEPS) -(LINE RINGING)
-(CELL PHONE BEEPS) -(라인 벨 울림)
Check if Min Junki and Carly Young's paths cross.
민준기인지 확인해보세요 그리고 Carly Young의 길은 교차합니다.
Get all his recent whereabouts and see if anything overlaps.
그의 최근 행방을 모두 알아내세요 그리고 겹치는 부분이 있는지 살펴보세요.
Yes. Bye.
예. 안녕.
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
It's just my hunch.
그냥 내 직감이야.
We just need to focus on Dominic.
우리는 도미닉에게만 집중하면 됩니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
TODAY WE ARE TOGETHER
TODAY WE ARE TOGETHER
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(휴대전화 진동)
Did I do something wrong again?
Did I do something wrong again?
But I didn't do anything.
하지만 나는 아무것도 하지 않았습니다.
Right?
오른쪽?
Be confident and bold.
자신감 있고 대담하게 행동하십시오.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
It's muggy, and I'm feeling under the weather.
후덥지근해요 그리고 기분이 좋지 않아.
I have so much work to do today.
오늘은 할 일이 너무 많아요.
I don't feel like eating. What's up?
먹고 싶지 않아요. 무슨 일이야?
You only had bread for breakfast.
아침에는 빵만 먹었어요.
You should eat well.
잘 먹어야 해요.
You're worried about me? What's happening?
나 걱정하는 거야? 무슨 일이야?
What's gotten into you?
당신에게 무슨 일이 생겼나요?
I'm always worried about you.
나는 항상 당신에 대해 걱정하고 있습니다.
I worry if you'd be skipping your meals
혹시 식사를 거르실까봐 걱정이 되네요
or you might get into an accident while driving.
아니면 사고를 당할 수도 있어요 운전하는 동안.
What if you get tired from dealing with people?
피곤하면 어쩌지 사람을 대하는 것부터?
Everything worries me.
모든 것이 나를 걱정합니다.
Oh, thank you.
아, 고마워요.
If you're not working overtime tonight, come home early.
오늘 밤에 초과근무를 하지 않는다면, 일찍 집에 오세요.
Why? Now that the truce is canceled, you want to fight again?
왜? 이제 휴전이 해제되었으니, 또 싸우고 싶어?
We didn't get Minseo in my ovulation period.
우리 민서 못받았어 내 배란 기간에.
(SCOFFS) You're right.
(비웃으며) 당신 말이 맞아요.
That reminds me. It was impossible to get pregnant that day.
그게 생각나네요. 불가능했어요 그날 임신을 하려고
Minseo was born despite the odds.
민서는 역경 속에서도 태어났다.
She's so vigorous
그녀는 너무 활발해요
because she was born despite the small chance.
그녀가 태어났기 때문에 작은 기회에도 불구하고.
(INHALES SHARPLY) I'm feeling it. I want it.
(가쁜 숨을 들이쉰다) 나는 그것을 느끼고 있다. 나는 그것을 원한다.
I want to challenge it.
나는 그것에 도전하고 싶다.
Okay. I'll get home early tonight. (CHUCKLES)
좋아요. 오늘 밤에는 집에 일찍 갈 거예요. (웃음)
Have a good day at work then.
그럼 직장에서 좋은 하루 보내세요.
Make sure not to skip your meal.
식사를 거르지 않도록 하세요.
You're hanging up already? Let's talk for some more.
벌써 전화 끊는 거야? 좀 더 이야기해보자.
Aren't you busy?
바쁘지 않나요?
Of course. I love talking to you on the phone outside.
물론. 나는 당신과 이야기하는 것을 좋아합니다 밖에서 전화로.
So are you going to stay outside forever?
그래서 당신은 하시겠습니까? 영원히 밖에 있어?
Okay. I'll get home early.
좋아요. 집에 일찍 갈게요.
Honey. I love you. I love you, darling.
꿀. 사랑해요. 사랑해요, 자기.
He's so simple.
그는 너무 단순해요.
Yes. That's how it should be.
예. 그렇게되어야합니다.
MAN: Don't run, go slowly.
MAN: 뛰지 말고 천천히 가세요.
Come here, hold hands.
이리 오세요, 손을 잡으세요.
Slowly.
느리게.
Oops.
이런.
Let's sit here.
여기 앉자.
What shall we get?
우리는 무엇을 얻을 것인가?
NAME CARLY YOUNG
이름은 칼리 영(Carly Young)
DOHOON: K88 in touch.
도훈: K88이 연락왔어요.
Of course. It's okay. Get everything you want.
물론. 괜찮아요. 원하는 모든 것을 얻으십시오.
-I'll get you all you want. -KID: Everything on the menu.
-I'll get you all you want. -KID: 메뉴의 모든 것.
KID 2: If we go abroad, we can't have this anymore?
KID 2: 해외에 나가면 we can't have this anymore?
No, you'll get even better food there.
No, you'll get even better food there.
KID 3: Really? CARLY: Of course.
아이 3: 정말요? 칼리: 물론이죠.
(KIDS CHEERING)
(아이들의 환호)
-(HUMMING) -(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
-(허밍) -(휴대폰이 진동함)
CHIEF OH: You said you were a heavy drinker.
오 사장: 그랬다고 했잖아 a heavy drinker.
But you passed out so fast.
그런데 너무 빨리 쓰러지셨어요.
Don't act so strong.
너무 강한 척 하지 마세요.
I caused you so much trouble, didn't I?
내가 널 너무 힘들게 했어, 그렇지?
CHIEF OH: You splashed alcohol on me and acted like a drunkard.
오과장: 너 나한테 술 뿌렸어 and acted like a drunkard.
-That's all. -Speak for yourself.
-그게 다야. -스스로 말해보세요.
(CHUCKLES)
(웃음)
Sorry if I caused you any trouble.
문제를 일으켰다면 죄송합니다.
Geez, when did she record that?
Geez, when did she record that?
Seriously.
진지하게.
CHIEF OH: You were so cute. I couldn't help but record it.
CHIEF OH: You were so cute. 기록하지 않을 수 없었습니다.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
I'll send you the cost for Qingdao and the postnatal center.
비용 보내드릴게요 칭다오 및 산후조리원에 대한 내용입니다.
Send me your account number.
계좌번호를 보내주세요.
What's she thinking?
그녀는 무슨 생각을 하고 있는 걸까요?
(MIRIM LAUGHS)
(MIRIM LAUGHS)
Father.
Father.
-Yura. -(EXCITED CHATTER)
-유라. -(흥분된 잡담)
MIRIM: I knew you were generous,
MIRIM: 당신이 관대하다는 걸 알고 있었어요.
but I didn't know you'd go this far.
하지만 당신이 이렇게까지 갈 줄은 몰랐어요.
Yura.
유라.
I'm not sure if I can take this.
내가 이것을 받아들일 수 있을지 잘 모르겠습니다.
Take what?
무엇을 가져갈까요?
JIHOON: Don't act like you don't know.
지훈: 모르는 척 하지 마세요.
Chief Oh told us.
오 과장이 우리에게 말했다.
Chief Oh?
아 과장?
You told her if she's going to pay, she better make it good.
You told her if she's going to pay, she better make it good.
She just called and said she upgraded
She just called and said she upgraded
Dad's seat to first class.
일등석으로 가는 아빠의 자리.
Thanks to you, I get to fly to Qingdao on a bed.
덕분에 날아갈 수 있어 침대 위에서 칭다오로.
Suite room and a limo tour.
스위트룸과 리무진 투어.
I'm getting ahead. (LAUGHS)
나는 앞서 가고 있다. (웃음)
I'll be getting a whole body massage in the postnatal center every day.
전신 마사지를 받을 거예요 in the postnatal center every day.
From now on, my role model is you.
이제부터 내 롤모델은 당신이에요.
Chief Oh sows,
오 과장은 씨를 뿌리고,
and you reap. (CLICKS TONGUE)
그리고 당신은 수확합니다. (혀를 클릭함)
(LAUGHS) Let's give it up for her.
(웃음) 그녀를 위해 포기하자.
-(ALL CLAPPING) -(YURA LAUGHING)
-(ALL CLAPPING) -(유라 웃음)
MIRIM: Come on.
미림: 어서요.
JIHOON: She must be embarrassed.
지훈: 당황스러울 것 같아요.
-She rushed in. -I know.
- 그녀는 서둘러 들어갔다. - 알아요.
-Sit inside. -Thanks.
-안에 앉으세요. -감사해요.
YURA: Oh, you don't have to.
유라: 아, 그럴 필요는 없어요.
But since you don't feel comfortable,
하지만 마음이 편하지 않으니까,
9,500,000 won. I'm sending you my account number.
9,500,000원. 제 계좌번호를 보내드리겠습니다.
What a lunatic.
정말 미치광이.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
YURA: I'll send it to you right away.
유라: 지금 바로 보내드릴게요.
I'll pay you 600,000 won on the first
첫 번째에 600,000원을 지불하겠습니다.
-of every month for 36 months. -(LAUGHING)
-36개월 동안 매월. -(웃음)
-She's funny. -Dominic's tough.
- 그 사람 재밌어요. -도미닉은 힘들어요.
He has so many disguised identities.
그 사람은 위장된 신분을 너무 많이 가지고 있어요.
This prick... (SIGHS)
이 새끼... (한숨)
He'll give us a pain in the neck when he enters Korea.
그 사람은 우리에게 목을 아프게 할 거야 그가 한국에 입국할 때.
So we must get rid of him now.
그러므로 우리는 지금 그를 제거해야 합니다.
Some say he was in the MI6.
어떤 사람들은 그가 MI6에 있었다고 말합니다.
Some say he was in Mossad.
어떤 사람들은 그가 모사드에 있었다고 말합니다.
If Interpol suffered this much,
인터폴이 이만큼 피해를 입었다면
are you sure we don't need backup?
백업이 필요하지 않은 게 확실해요?
It's better for just us to move.
우리만 이사하는 것이 낫습니다.
Our goal is to dig into the group through Dominic,
우리의 목표는 그룹을 파헤치는 것입니다. 도미닉을 통해
but in the worst case scenario,
하지만 최악의 경우에는
we'd have to kill him.
우리는 그를 죽여야 할 것입니다.
(IN ENGLISH) Okay.
(영어로) 알았어.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
(학생들의 잡담)
(IN KOREAN) Guys. Focus.
(한국어) 여러분. 집중하다.
You're finally performing tomorrow.
드디어 내일 공연이군요.
Aren't you all nervous?
다들 긴장하지 않으셨나요?
-STUDENTS: Yes. -Yes.
-학생: 네. -예.
When your parents come tomorrow,
내일 부모님 오시면
just show them what you worked on.
당신이 무슨 일을 했는지 보여주세요.
Don't be nervous.
긴장하지 마세요.
STUDENTS: Okay.
학생: 좋아요.
Don't pull Seoyeon's costume.
서연 의상은 당기지 마세요.
-(SIGHS) He ripped it. -My gosh.
-(한숨) 그 사람이 그걸 찢었어요. -맙소사.
The performance is tomorrow. Why would you rip it?
공연은 내일이에요. 왜 그걸 찢어버리겠어요?
STUDENT: What do we do? The performance is tomorrow.
학생: 우리는 무엇을 하나요? 공연은 내일이에요.
What do I do?
어떻게 해야 하나요?
For me?
나를 위한?
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(휴대폰이 진동함)
STUDENT 2: Hello? Mom.
학생 2: 안녕하세요? 엄마.
Okay.
좋아요.
Mr. Song. My mom's here.
송 씨. 우리 엄마가 여기 있어요.
STUDENTS: Bye.
학생: 안녕.
Guys.
얘들아.
Bye.
안녕.
Go to bed early tonight. Minseo. Take care of your throat.
오늘 밤에는 일찍 잠자리에 드세요. 민서. 목을 조심하세요.
Drink a lot of water. Don't be late.
물을 많이 마시세요. 늦지 마세요.
I better watch my throat.
목을 조심하는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(장난스러운 음악 재생)
I'm going this way.
나는 이쪽으로 갈 것이다.
Then I'll go that way too.
그럼 나도 그쪽으로 갈게.
Don't you live in that direction?
당신은 그 방향으로 살고 있지 않습니까?
The Earth is round.
지구는 둥글다.
I'll get home one day.
나는 어느 날 집에 갈 것이다.
Thank you for today.
오늘은 감사합니다.
For what?
무엇을 위해?
You were pretty cool.
당신은 정말 멋졌어요.
You're cool too.
You're cool too.
When I fell, you carried me to the nurse's office.
내가 넘어졌을 때 당신이 날 안고 가줬어요 간호사실로.
So that makes us both cool.
그래서 우리 둘 다 멋져요.
It's nice.
좋네요.
You like cool women, don't you?
당신은 멋진 여자를 좋아하지 않나요?
(DISTANT BELL TOLLING)
(먼 종소리)
-MAN: Father. -Welcome.
-MAN: Father. -환영.
-How have you been? -Good.
- 잘 지냈어요? -좋은.
Here.
여기.
CARLY: (ON EARPIECE) Finally.
칼리: (이어피스를 통해) 드디어요.
MAN: Even if you can't make it to our wedding,
MAN: 네가 할 수 없더라도 우리 결혼식에 가세요.
I wanted to give you the invitation.
초대장을 드리고 싶었어요.
Thank you, Father.
감사합니다, 아버지.
Because you've been diligent and kind,
부지런하고 친절하셨기 때문에
this good day arrived.
this good day arrived.
WOMAN: Do you have to go?
여자: 꼭 가야 해요?
I feel like if you go, we'll never meet again.
가보면 좋을 것 같은 느낌 we'll never meet again.
Why not?
왜 안 돼?
You can always come and visit me.
언제든지 저를 방문하실 수 있습니다.
Did you give everyone in church the invitations?
교회에 있는 모든 사람을 주셨습니까? 초대장?
WOMAN: Brother Sungchan and Sister Jaesun and Yukyung are coming.
WOMAN: 성찬오빠와 Sister Jaesun and Yukyung are coming.
It'll be a family reunion.
It'll be a family reunion.
You should come in for some tea.
차 좀 마시러 오셔야 해요.
Come in.
들어오세요.
MAN AND WOMAN: Yes.
남자와 여자: 네.
CARLY: Let's go.
칼리: 가자.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(휴대폰 신호음)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(휴대전화 진동)
KWON DOHOON
권도훈
-Yes. -Carly Young.
- 네. -Carly Young.
Are you sure he's on red alert?
Are you sure he's on red alert?
It's all been confirmed.
모두 확인되었습니다.
You think we didn't even check?
You think we didn't even check?
(SIGHS) I don't normally take
(SIGHS) I don't normally take
the ambiguous ones.
모호한 것.
So I told you not to check on him.
그래서 내가 그 사람을 확인하지 말라고 했어요.
After disguising as a missionary,
선교사로 변장한 후,
maybe he thinks he's a real missionary.
어쩌면 그는 자신이 진짜 선교사라고 생각할지도 모릅니다.
He's dirty anyway.
He's dirty anyway.
Don't fall for his disguise.
Don't fall for his disguise.
Finish your investigation.
조사를 마치세요.
-(LINE DISCONNECTS) -What's wrong?
-(라인 연결 끊김) - 무슨 일이야?
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
I got Dominic's photo.
도미닉의 사진을 받았어요.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(자동차 엔진이 시동됨)
(LOW SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(낮은 긴장감 있는 음악 재생)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(엘리베이터 소리)
Please change into a gown,
가운으로 갈아입고,
and press the bell when you're ready.
그리고 준비가 되면 벨을 누르세요.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(감동적인 음악이 계속됩니다)
(FIRES GUN)
(총 발사)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
(문을 두드린다)
MAN: Sir, may I go in?
MAN: 선생님, 들어가도 될까요?
Yes, I'll get changed soon.
응, 금방 갈아입을게.
MAN: Okay.
남자: 알았어.
Good.
좋은.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(HUMMING SOFTLY)
(부드럽게 흥얼거림)
Mom.
엄마.
Mom, fix this for me.
엄마, 이거 좀 고쳐주세요.
Hurry.
서두르다.
(SEWING MACHINE WHIRRING)
(재봉틀이 윙윙거리는 소리)
You know, there are 10 girls in the class.
아시다시피, 거기에는 같은 반에 여학생 10명.
And I'm the only one who got his candy.
그리고 그 사람 사탕을 받은 사람은 나뿐이었어.
Just for me.
나를 위해서만.
Why did he do that?
왜 그랬나요?
I wonder.
궁금해요.
Why did Boseok do that?
보석은 왜 그랬을까?
I don't know.
모르겠습니다.
Other girls must've been so jealous, right?
다른 여자들도 그랬겠지 너무 질투심이 많았지, 그렇지?
Yes. Boseok's the most popular in the class.
예. Boseok's the most popular 수업 중.
(CANDY WRAPPER RUSTLING)
(사탕 포장지 바스락거림)
I suddenly want a candy.
I suddenly want a candy.
Can I have it?
가질 수 있나요?
Please? I want a candy.
제발? 나는 사탕을 원한다.
Sorry, Mom.
Sorry, Mom.
This is inedible.
This is inedible.
It's Boseok's heart.
It's Boseok's heart.
-(DOOR OPENS) -(DOHOON HUMMING)
-(DOOR OPENS) -(도훈 허밍)
Honey!
여보!
(DOHOON LAUGHING)
(도훈 웃음)
MINSEO: Dad. YURA: You're home.
MINSEO: Dad. 유라: 당신은 집에 있어요.
DOHOON: Minseo.
도훈: 민서.
What's that?
그게 뭐야?
-(SIGHS) -(WHIRRING CONTINUES)
-(한숨) -(WHIRRING CONTINUES)
What's that? What are you doing?
그게 뭐야? 뭐하세요?
That's wrong.
그건 틀렸어.
So wrong. (CHUCKLES)
정말 틀렸어요. (웃음)
(TIGER GROWLING)
(호랑이 으르렁거림)
(CHEERING LOUDLY)
(큰 소리로 환호함)
You're the coolest in the whole wide world.
You're the coolest in the whole wide world.
Whoa! You look awesome.
와! 당신 정말 멋져 보여요.
Minseo. You look so charismatic.
민서. You look so charismatic.
It's wonderful. (CHUCKLES)
정말 훌륭해요. (웃음)
Isn't it wonderful?
정말 멋지지 않나요?
Now, it's time to go. Let's go.
Now, it's time to go. 갑시다.
Mom, can you add more shoulder pads?
엄마, 어깨패드 더 추가해주실 수 있나요?
And it'll look cool with glowing stickers.
그리고 멋져 보일 거야 빛나는 스티커와 함께.
Any other requests?
다른 요청은 없나요?
MINSEO: That's all for now.
민서: 지금은 그게 다예요.
Okay.
좋아요.
DOHOON: Minseo. Daddy's disappointed.
도훈: 민서. 아빠는 실망했어요.
MINSEO: Why?
민서: 왜요?
I thought
나는 생각했다
you were a matured first grader.
너는 성숙한 1학년이었어.
You're not in kindergarten anymore.
당신은 더 이상 유치원에 있지 않습니다.
Then you should be able to
그렇다면 당신은 할 수 있어야합니다
stitch that on your own.
직접 꿰매세요.
No first grader can sew on their own.
1학년 학생은 스스로 바느질을 할 수 없습니다.
(GASPS) Then you'll be the first one in the world.
(GASPS) 그러면 당신은 세계 최초.
You can do that.
그렇게 할 수 있습니다.
You always ask Mom
넌 항상 엄마한테 물어보잖아
to sew a button.
단추를 꿰매려고.
That's a matter between Mom and Dad.
그건 엄마 아빠 사이의 문제예요.
Whatever. Mom likes me more than you.
무엇이든. 엄마는 너보다 나를 더 좋아해.
Never ever.
절대로.
Mom likes Daddy more.
엄마는 아빠를 더 좋아해요.
Right, honey?
그렇지, 얘야?
No. You like me more, right?
아뇨. 당신이 나를 더 좋아하죠?
DOHOON: No, right?
도훈: 아니, 그렇지?
You like me more. Say you do.
당신은 나를 더 좋아합니다. 그렇다고 말해보세요.
-No, you like me more, right? -YURA: Yes.
-아니, 네가 더 좋아하는 거 맞지? -유라: 그렇죠.
Stop it.
그만해요.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
(소프트 음악 재생)
(DOHOON GROANING)
(도훈이 끙끙거림)
Why do you always want to sleep with me?
왜 항상 나랑 자고 싶어?
(YAWNING)
(하품)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(음악은 계속됩니다)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(문이 닫힘)
(DOHOON GROANING)
(도훈이 끙끙거림)
Honey.
여보.
I'm really curious.
정말 궁금해요.
Is it impossible for a couple
부부라면 불가능한가?
to do it for once?
한번 해볼까?
(YAWNING)
(하품)
If you know of anyone, please ask if it's the same for other families too.
혹시 아시는 분 계시면 물어보세요 다른 가족들도 마찬가지라면.
-(DOOR OPENS) -(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
-(문이 열린다) -(달리는 발자국)
How come she never sleeps?
그녀는 왜 잠을 자지 않는 걸까요?
(GROANS)
(신음소리)
Gosh. How come...
이런. 어쩌다...
(DOOR CLOSES)
(문이 닫힘)
(DOHOON GROANS)
(도훈이 신음)
-...she never sleeps? -(YURA GROANS)
-...잠도 안 자고? -(유라가 신음)
Minseo, brush your teeth.
민서야, 양치를 해라.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(휴대전화 진동)
DOHOON: Oh. What's this?
도훈: 아. 이건 뭐죠?
(GROANS, SNIFFLES)
(신음소리, 훌쩍거림)
(IN GERMAN) Hey, Wolfe! It's been ages.
(독일어로) 안녕, 울프! 오랜 세월이 흘렀습니다.
You came to Korea? Today?
한국에 오셨나요? 오늘?
We should definitely meet. Hold on.
우리 꼭 만나야 해요. 기다리다.
(IN KOREAN) It's a friend of mine. Can he come to Minseo's school?
(한국어) 제 친구예요. 민서네 학교에 올 수 있을까?
(IN GERMAN) Why don't you come to our daughter's play?
(독일어) 왜 안 오세요? 우리 딸 놀이에?
I'll introduce you to our family.
우리 가족을 소개할게요.
I'll send you the address. Call me when you arrive.
주소를 보내드리겠습니다. 도착하면 전화해 주세요.
It's so good to talk to you, see you soon.
당신과 이야기를 나누는 것이 너무 좋습니다. 곧 뵙겠습니다.
(CHUCKLES)
(웃음)
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(라인 연결 끊김)
(IN KOREAN) I lost contact with him a long time ago.
(한국어) 그 사람과 연락이 끊겼어요 오래 전.
He arrived in Korea today.
오늘 한국에 도착했습니다.
Gosh. He was alive after all.
이런. 결국 그는 살아있었습니다.
THEATER FESTIVAL
연극 축제
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(경쾌한 음악 재생)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(무뚝뚝한 잡담)
You may go in.
들어가셔도 됩니다.
This way please.
이쪽으로 부탁드립니다.
Off the stage.
무대에서.
Class One. Sit here.
클래스 1. 여기 앉으세요.
Class One. Sit here please.
클래스 1. 여기 앉아주세요.
Class One sits here.
1학년이 여기 앉습니다.
Is everyone here?
모두 여기 있나요?
STUDENTS: Yes.
학생: 네.
Boseok and Minseo. Stand up.
보석이랑 민서. 일어서세요.
-Yes.
-예.
(STUDENTS CHEERING)
(학생들의 환호)
It's all good,
다 괜찮아요
but it's too flashy.
하지만 너무 화려해요.
Can you at least remove the tiger on your back?
최소한 호랑이를 제거할 수 있나요? on your back?
What? But my mom stitched it all night.
무엇? 그런데 엄마가 밤새도록 꿰매셨어요.
You need to be in balance with Zorro.
Zorro와 균형을 유지해야 합니다.
Our hero is Zorro.
우리의 영웅은 조로입니다.
(STUDENTS EXCLAIMING IN AWE)
(학생들이 경외감을 표시함)
STUDENT 1: Did your mom make it?
학생 1: 엄마가 만드셨나요?
I want it too.
나도 그것을 원해요.
-I want it. -Me too.
- 나는 그것을 원한다. -저도요.
Me too.
저도요.
-Give me one. -Me too.
-Give me one. -저도요.
(PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(장난스러운 음악 재생)
You can take it.
당신은 그것을 가져갈 수 있습니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
You're welcome.
천만에요.
I guess the award really works.
수상이 정말 효과가 있는 것 같아요.
STUDENTS: Wow. Minseo's so cool.
학생: 와우. 민서 정말 멋있어요.
Yes.
예.
-So cool. -You're so cool.
- 정말 멋지네요. -정말 멋지네요.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(다가오는 발자국)
The principal wants to see you.
교장선생님이 당신을 보고 싶어하십니다.
What?
무엇?
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(발자국이 멀어진다)
What did you say? The school superintendent's coming?
뭐라고 했어? 학교 교감이 오나요?
But this is just a small talent show.
But this is just a small talent show.
He's going to take photos
그 사람은 사진을 찍을 거예요
and run it in the local newspaper.
지역 신문에 실어보세요.
Make sure not to make any mistakes.
실수하지 않도록 하세요.
In the newspaper too?
In the newspaper too?
But it's not that big...
하지만 그리 크지는 않은데...
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
His term is almost over.
그의 임기가 거의 끝났다.
So he's nosing here and there.
그래서 여기저기서 코를 킁킁대고 있어요.
What can I do? I have to play along.
어떻게 해야 하나요? 나도 같이 놀아야 해.
He's my old buddy.
그 사람은 내 오랜 친구예요.
We get that he's your friend,
우리는 그가 당신의 친구라는 것을 알고 있습니다.
but this was never expected.
그러나 이것은 결코 예상되지 않았습니다.
It's not like he's visiting his friend.
그가 친구를 방문하는 것과는 다릅니다.
Don't feel pressured.
압박감을 느끼지 마십시오.
I'm sure the kids will do well.
아이들이 잘 할 거라고 확신해요.
They've been practicing for a long time.
They've been practicing for a long time.
We spent a lot of budget on it.
우리는 그것에 많은 예산을 썼습니다.
You know that, right?
그거 알지?
The Three Little Pigs used a lot of money.
아기돼지 삼형제 used a lot of money.
No, we didn't spend that much.
No, we didn't spend that much.
Well The Zorro team used wires, right?
음, Zorro 팀은 전선을 사용했지요, 그렇죠?
You even had stunt coordinators.
스턴트 코디네이터도 있었죠.
The budget plan seemed a little weird.
예산 계획이 좀 이상한 것 같았습니다.
No, the budget, he--
아니, 예산이요, 그는--
PRINCIPAL: That's enough.
PRINCIPAL: That's enough.
Remember. No mistakes.
기억하다. 실수는 없습니다.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
Class One. Gather around.
클래스 1. 모여라.
Class One. Zorro.
클래스 1. Zorro.
Zorro. Boseok.
Zorro. 보석.
Minseo, come here.
민서야, 이리 와봐.
Boseok and Minseo. Come here.
보석이랑 민서. 이리 오세요.
Let's recite the lines.
대사를 암송해 봅시다.
Blame me for taking so long.
너무 오래 걸린 것에 대해 나를 비난하십시오.
Oh, Lolita.
아, 로리타.
Oh, Zorro. I don't blame you.
아, 조로. I don't blame you.
Zorro. I--
Zorro. 나는--
Die, Zorro. Die.
죽어라, 조로. 주사위.
(IN ENGLISH) Stop, stop.
(IN ENGLISH) Stop, stop.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(IN KOREAN) I don't feel any emotions.
(한국어) 아무런 감정도 느끼지 않습니다.
You need to add more emotion in there.
거기에 감정을 더 추가해야 합니다.
"Die. Die!"
"죽어라. 죽어라!"
Can you do it? Want to try again?
당신은 그것을 할 수 있습니까? 다시 시도하고 싶나요?
-Die. Die. -Stop. Stop.
-주사위. 주사위. -멈추다. 멈추다.
What do I do? That's the climax.
어떻게 해야 하나요? 그것이 클라이막스입니다.
Die, Zorro. Die.
죽어라, 조로. 주사위.
Oh, Zorro. I don't blame you.
아, 조로. 나는 당신을 비난하지 않습니다.
(STUDENTS CONTINUE CHATTERING)
(STUDENTS CONTINUE CHATTERING)
Should I make Zorro kiss the princess?
Should I make Zorro kiss the princess?
Wait. What's wrong with the light?
기다리다. 빛에 무슨 문제가 있나요?
Guys. Let's get off the stage for a second. Let's go.
얘들아. Let's get off the stage 잠시 동안. 갑시다.
MIRIM: (LAUGHS) Look at Minseo.
미림: (웃음) 민서 좀 보세요.
JIHOON: Look at her eyebrows.
지훈: 눈썹 좀 보세요.
MIRIM: She's so cute.
미림: 정말 귀여워요.
-Take a picture of me here. -Okay.
- 여기서 사진 좀 찍어주세요. -좋아요.
-Hey. -It's not about you today.
-여기요. -오늘은 당신 얘기가 아니에요.
-I asked you to take a photo of me. -We're here already.
- 사진 좀 찍어달라고 했어요. -우리는 이미 여기에 있습니다.
What? You can't make it?
무엇? You can't make it?
Come to the assembly hall. Call me when you get here.
집회장으로 오세요. 여기 도착하면 전화해.
See you soon.
곧 봐요.
He'll be here before the play ends.
그 사람은 연극이 끝나기 전에 여기에 올 거예요.
I won't believe him until he gets here.
그 사람이 여기 올 때까지 난 그 사람을 믿지 않을 거예요.
Where's Minseo?
민서는 어디 있어요?
I want to take a photo with the future movie star.
사진을 찍고 싶어요 미래의 영화배우와 함께.
-I'll look for her. -Okay.
- 제가 찾아볼게요. -좋아요.
Father, the future actress is here.
아버지, 미래의 배우가 여기 있습니다.
-There she is. -(MIRIM LAUGHS)
- 저기 있어요. -(미림이 웃는다)
Come here.
Come here.
-A photo? -Yes.
-사진요? -예.
-JIHOON: I'll take it for you. -With this, at least.
-지훈: 제가 가져갈게요. -적어도 이것으로는요.
-Make us look tall. -JIHOON: All right.
- 키가 커 보이도록 해주세요. -지훈: 그렇죠.
-One, two, three. -Make us look good.
-하나 둘 셋. - 우리를 좋게 보이게 해주세요.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(둘 다 투덜거림)
STUDENT: Mr. Song told us to come for rehearsal.
학생: 송 선생님이 우리에게 말씀하셨어요. 리허설을 하러 오세요.
-Okay. -I'm coming.
-좋아요. -나 간다.
Minseo.
민서.
Minseo, this is bad.
민서야, 이건 나빠.
Don't disturb me. I'm focusing here.
방해하지 마세요. I'm focusing here.
Boseok and Jihee are going to kiss.
보석과 지희가 키스를 하려고 합니다.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(극적인 음악 연주)
There's a kiss scene between Zorro and Lolita.
키스신이 나오네요 조로와 로리타 사이.
What are you going to do?
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
(YURA GASPS SOFTLY)
(유라가 작게 헐떡인다)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(감동적인 음악 재생)
I want to go home.
나는 집에 가고 싶다.
I can't act like this.
나는 이렇게 행동할 수 없다.
YURA: Minseo.
유라: 민서.
Calm down and listen.
진정하고 들어보세요.
I'm dying and Boseok's kissing someone else.
나는 죽어 가고있다 그리고 보석은 다른 사람과 키스를 해요.
I'm disappointed. I'm going home.
나는 실망했다. 나는 집에 갈거야.
-No. -Minseo.
-아니요. -민서.
Minseo. Where's your homeroom teacher?
민서. 담임선생님은 어디 계시나요?
One word from me, and he won't be able to do that. Where's your teacher?
나한테 한 마디만 하면 그 사람은 못 할 거야 to do that. 선생님은 어디 계시나요?
How dare he upset my Minseo?
그 사람이 어떻게 감히 내 민서를 화나게 했어?
I won't let him get away with it.
나는 그 사람이 그걸 그냥 넘어가도록 놔두지 않을 거예요.
MIRIM: I've got an idea.
MIRIM: I've got an idea.
How about stabbing Lolita with your knife?
How about stabbing Lolita 칼로?
You have to win love.
사랑을 이겨야 합니다.
Okay?
좋아요?
JIHOON: No.
지훈: 아니요.
It's better to stab Boseok instead.
It's better to stab Boseok instead.
Minseo, you're strong.
민서 씨, 당신은 강해요.
Go stab him and make him pass out.
가서 그를 찔러 기절시키세요.
Then he can't kiss her.
그러면 그는 그녀에게 키스할 수 없습니다.
That's too cruel.
너무 잔인해요.
YURA: Jihoon. Mirim.
유라: 지훈이요. 미림.
Minseo. Boseok likes you because you're cool.
민서. 보석이는 네가 멋있어서 좋아한다.
Even if you're upset, if you still act like a pro,
당황스러워도, 아직도 프로처럼 행동한다면
he'll like you even more.
그 사람은 당신을 더욱 좋아할 거예요.
Right? Right?
오른쪽? 오른쪽?
ALL: Yes. MINSEO: No.
전체: 그렇습니다. 민서: 아니요.
(CRYING)
(울음)
Hey. No calls from Dohoon yet?
안녕. 도훈이한테 아직 전화가 없나요?
No. Maybe he's driving. He doesn't even read my texts.
아뇨. 어쩌면 그 사람이 운전하고 있을지도 모르죠. 그 사람은 내 문자도 읽지 않아요.
Minseo. Stop crying.
민서. Stop crying.
I hate plays more than anything in the world.
I hate plays more than anything in the world.
I hate it.
나는 그것을 싫어한다.
She's acting up.
그녀는 행동하고 있습니다.
No one but Dohoon can control her.
No one but Dohoon can control her.
-Call him until he picks up. -Okay.
- 그가 전화를 받을 때까지 전화하세요. -좋아요.
We must stop her before she loses it.
We must stop her before she loses it.
Mirim, join him.
미림, 그와 합류해라.
-Yes, Father. -MINSEO: No.
-네, 아버지. -민서: 아니요.
Why isn't he picking up?
그 사람은 왜 전화를 안 받나요?
Two, three. Get up. Up.
둘, 셋. 일어나세요. 위로.
MIRIM: What's his number?
MIRIM: 그 사람 전화번호는 몇 번이에요?
JIHOON: You don't even know his... YURA: Oh!
JIHOON: You don't even know his... 유라: 아!
-Minseo.
-민서.
CHIEF OH
오 과장
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(휴대전화 진동)
(VIBRATING STOPS)
(진동 정지)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(감동적인 음악 재생)
CHIEF OH
오 과장
-(CELL PHONE BEEPS) -(LINE RINGING)
-(CELL PHONE BEEPS) -(라인 벨 울림)
CHIEF OH: If it's not urgent, call me later.
오 수석: If it's not urgent, call me later.
I couldn't check the last part.
마지막 부분은 확인하지 못했습니다.
You know why?
이유를 아시나요?
Information from the head office must be true.
본사에서 제공하는 정보 사실이어야 합니다.
Carly Young retired a few years ago.
칼리 영(Carly Young)은 몇 년 전에 은퇴했습니다.
Why don't we report to the head office
본사에 보고하는 게 어때?
and wait?
그리고 잠깐?
The head office already made the decision. Finish him.
본사는 이미 만들어놨어요 the decision. 그를 끝내세요.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(라인 연결 끊김)
-(CELL PHONE VIBRATING) -Oh.
-(휴대전화 진동) -Oh.
WOMAN: (ON PHONE) I've looked up what you asked.
WOMAN: (ON PHONE) 질문하신 내용을 찾아보았습니다.
It was Carly Young
칼리 영이었어
who helped Min Junki enter Korea.
민준이의 한국 입국을 도와준 사람.
I emailed the details just now.
지금 막 자세한 내용을 이메일로 보냈습니다.
He entered Korea last year.
지난해 한국에 입국했다.
Yes, they have been in touch for eight months to be precise.
네, 연락이 왔습니다 정확히는 8개월 동안.
And no connections abroad.
그리고 해외에서는 연결이 없습니다.
Any changes on Carly Young's departure date?
모든 변경 사항 칼리 영의 출발 날짜는요?
One second.
1초.
Nothing.
아무것도 아님.
Flight at 7 a.m. tomorrow.
내일 오전 7시 비행기.
I thought Dohoon was going to handle him today.
도훈이가 그럴 줄 알았는데 오늘 그 사람을 처리해.
Okay. I'll call you back.
좋아요. 다시 전화할게요.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
What if Dominic was trying to meet Carly Young?
만약 도미니크가 그랬다면? 칼리 영을 만나려고 하시나요?
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
How long until Dominic's boat arrives?
Dominic의 보트가 도착할 때까지 얼마나 걸리나요?
About an hour.
약 1시간.
Let's place our agents here.
여기에 요원을 배치합시다.
-We're going to Seoul. -All of a sudden?
- 우리는 서울로 갑니다. -갑자기요?
I'll explain on the way.
가는 길에 설명하겠습니다.
Dominic might be in Korea already.
도미닉은 이미 한국에 있을 수도 있어요.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(무뚝뚝한 잡담)
-Hello.
-안녕하세요.
Minseo.
민서.
Do you know Minseo?
Do you know Minseo?
She's very playful...
그녀는 매우 장난스럽습니다...
That one.
그거.
That's her. She looks just like this.
That's her. 그녀는 이렇게 생겼습니다.
Minseo.
민서.
Kwon Minseo.
권민서.
-Minseo. -(PA SYSTEM CHIMES)
-민서. -(PA 시스템 차임벨)
(ON PA) Neuru Elementary School Theater Festival will start shortly.
(ON PA) 느루초등학교 연극제가 곧 시작됩니다.
All families and visitors, please be seated.
All families and visitors, please be seated.
No. I'm not doing it.
아뇨. 안 할 거예요.
(SIGHS)
(한숨)
(PA SYSTEM CHIMES)
(PA 시스템 차임벨)
(ON PA) I repeat.
(ON PA) 반복합니다.
Neuru Elementary School Theater Festival will start shortly.
느루초등학교 연극제 will start shortly.
All families and visitors, please be seated.
가족과 방문객 모두, 자리에 앉으시기 바랍니다.
Mom, what are you doing?
엄마, 뭐하세요?
I'm trying to understand how you feel.
I'm trying to understand how you feel.
No wonder you don't want to act.
당신이 행동하고 싶지 않은 것도 당연합니다.
You gave him the cool cape,
당신은 그에게 멋진 망토를 주었습니다.
and he's kissing some other girl with it?
그리고 그 사람이 키스하고 있어 다른 여자랑 같이 있어?
That is just wrong. That must not happen.
그것은 단지 잘못된 것입니다. 그런 일이 일어나서는 안 됩니다.
Forget about acting.
연기는 잊어버리세요.
Let's just go home.
그냥 집에 가자.
Still...
아직도...
That's...
그건...
-What about the play? -(SIGHS)
- 연극은 어때요? -(한숨)
Who cares? Your feelings matter the most.
누가 신경쓰나요? 당신의 감정이 가장 중요합니다.
Mom, think about it.
엄마, 생각해 보세요.
Without a villain, Zorro would be nothing.
악당이 없으면, 조로는 아무것도 아닐 것이다.
Is that how it works?
그게 작동하는 방식인가요?
Yes.
예.
A villain is very important.
악당은 매우 중요합니다.
Still, no.
그래도 안돼.
Too upset to act.
행동하기엔 너무 화가 났습니다.
Remember what Dad said?
아빠가 한 말 기억나?
A true actor
진정한 배우
never takes the stage personally.
결코 개인적으로 무대에 오르지 않습니다.
That leaves me no choice.
그것은 나에게 선택의 여지가 없습니다.
Get up.
일어나세요.
Oh, Minseo.
아, 민서.
You're pretty cool.
당신은 정말 멋지군요.
I'll go ahead.
나는 계속할 것이다.
You should come and watch me.
당신은 와서 나를 지켜봐야합니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
(깊은 한숨)
(GROANS)
(신음소리)
-(ELEVATOR DINGS) -AUTOMATED VOICE: Going up.
-(엘리베이터 소리) -자동 음성: 올라갑니다.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(감동적인 음악 재생)
-(IMPERCEPTIBLE) -(MUSIC CONTINUES)
-(인식할 수 없음) -(음악은 계속됩니다)
(EXHALES)
(숨을 내쉬다)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(휴대전화 진동)
A change of plan.
계획 변경.
We're capturing Carly Young alive.
우리는 칼리 영을 생포하고 있습니다.
I'm on my way to Seoul.
저는 서울로 가는 중이에요.
I'll go in with Team C. You may withdraw.
저는 C팀으로 가겠습니다. 철회할 수 있습니다.
-What's the reason? -I'll tell you later.
-이유는 무엇입니까? -나중에 말씀드리겠습니다.
Got it.
알았어요.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(라인 연결 끊김)
Yes. Promise you'll come visit me.
그렇습니다. 나를 방문하겠다고 약속해주세요.
You're welcome any time.
언제든지 환영합니다.
I'm staying near the airport tonight and flying tomorrow at 7 a.m.
나 오늘 밤 공항 근처에 묵을 거야 그리고 내일 오전 7시에 비행기를 타요
Yes. Bye.
그렇습니다. 안녕.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
(감동적인 음악이 계속됩니다)
Why would the Union...
연합은 왜...
Why?
왜요?
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
(휴대폰 신호음)
(IN ENGLISH) Carly Young's taken care of.
(영어) 칼리 영이 보살핌을 받았어요.
Yeah, I talked to Min Junki and confirmed the location of them all.
응, 민준기랑 얘기했어 그리고 모두의 위치를 ​​확인했다.
Consider the job done.
완료된 작업을 고려하십시오.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(극적인 음악 재생)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
(청중의 환호)
(IN KOREAN) Where's Raymond?
(IN KOREAN) Where's Raymond?
Raymond?
레이먼드?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
It's Minseo.
민서예요.
Raymond, no point in wasting your energy.
레이먼드, 말이 안 돼 에너지를 낭비하고 있습니다.
Everything's been determined.
Everything's been determined.
Nothing's been determined between you and me.
아직 결정된 건 없어 너와 나 사이.
Die!
주사위!
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING IN AWE)
(경외감에 환호하는 청중)
(YELLING)
(고함)
(YELLS)
(소리친다)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
Good.
좋아요.
(IMPERCEPTIBLE CONVERSATION)
(눈에 띄지 않는 대화)
(BOTH YELLING)
(둘 다 소리친다)
(MIRIM EXCLAIMS SADLY)
(미림이 슬프게 외친다)
Raymond. Our ill-fated relationship ends here.
레이몬드. 우리의 불행한 관계는 여기서 끝이다.
(YELLS)
(소리친다)
Zorro, I'm not going to forgive you.
Zorro, I'm not going to forgive you.
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING) -(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
-(경쾌한 음악 재생) -(청중의 환호)
(APPLAUSE)
(박수)
She's good.
그녀는 좋다.
Yura, she's not a troublemaker anymore.
유라, 그 사람은 더 이상 말썽꾸러기가 아니다.
That's my daughter.
그 사람은 내 딸이에요.
All right. Focus.
괜찮은. 집중하다.
Stay alert to the end.
끝까지 주의를 기울이십시오.
You got this, Class One.
알겠습니다, 1학년.
STUDENTS: Yes.
학생: 네.
Let's wait in your positions.
당신의 위치에서 기다리자.
Yes.
예.
Boseok, are you going to kill me and kiss the princess?
보석아 나를 죽일 셈이냐 그리고 공주한테 키스해?
I have to.
그래야 해요.
Do you want to kiss Hwang Jihee?
황지희한테 키스할래?
No, I'm only pretending.
아뇨, 그냥 그런 척하는 중이에요.
What if you end up kissing her for real? What are you going to do then?
그녀에게 진짜로 키스하게 된다면 어떨까요? 그러면 당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
Then
그런 다음
it's too bad.
너무 나쁘다.
I'm asking you for one last time.
마지막으로 한 번만 부탁드리겠습니다.
I'm going to get stabbed and bleed to death,
찔리겠다 피를 흘리며 죽고,
and you're going to kiss Jihee in front of me?
그리고 넌 지희한테 키스할 거야 내 앞에?
I have to. The script was changed.
그래야 해요. 스크립트가 변경되었습니다.
(SIGHS) Fine. I'm changing my script.
(한숨) 좋아요. 스크립트를 변경 중입니다.
Boseok, what are you doing? You need to get on the stage. Let's go.
보석아, 뭐해? 무대에 올라야 해요. 갑시다.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Minseo, can you do it?
민서야, 할 수 있어?
-Yes, Mr. Song. -Let's go.
-네, 송 선생님. -갑시다.
That's my daughter. (LAUGHS)
그 사람은 내 딸이에요. (웃음)
NO ENTRY DURING PERFORMANCE
공연 중 입장 불가
What's this?
이건 뭐죠?
I forgot to buy flowers.
꽃 사는 걸 깜빡했어요.
Yura's going to yell at me.
유라가 나한테 소리칠 거야.
I'll go that way.
나는 그쪽으로 갈 것이다.
-(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) -(APPLAUSE)
-(극적인 음악 연주) -(박수)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(관객 환호)
Everything is over.
모든 것이 끝났습니다.
Never. Zorro never gives up.
절대. 조로는 결코 포기하지 않습니다.
Zorro.
조로.
I finally got you.
드디어 당신을 얻었습니다.
(YELLING)
(고함)
(AUDIENCE CHUCKLING)
(청중 웃음)
Raymond, it's over now.
레이먼드, 이제 끝났어
Zorro, you have to die.
조로, 넌 죽어야 해.
Raymond.
레이몬드.
Zorro.
조로.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(드라마틱한 음악이 계속됩니다)
Zorro!
조로!
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING AND APPLAUDING)
(청중의 환호와 박수)
You're over now.
이제 끝났습니다.
That's my line.
그게 내 라인이야.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES)
(드라마틱한 음악이 계속됩니다)
(YELLING)
(고함)
AUDIENCE: Oh!
청중: 오!
(BOTH YELL)
(둘 다 소리친다)
(AUDIENCE MURMURING IN AWE)
(청중이 경외감에 웅얼거림)
-(BOTH YELLING) -(SWORD SLASHES)
-(둘 다 고함) -(칼 슬래시)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING AND APPLAUDING)
(청중의 환호와 박수)
Lolita, it's over now.
롤리타, 이제 끝났어.
Zorro, I knew you were our hope.
조로, 당신이 우리의 희망이라는 걸 알았습니다.
You made it possible, Lolita.
당신이 그것을 가능하게 만들었어요, 롤리타.
Zorro, my hope.
조로, 내 희망.
-Zorro. -Lolita.
-조로. -로리타.
-Zorro. Zorro. -Lolita. Lolita.
-조로. 조로. -로리타. 로리타.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(청중 박수)
How about stabbing Lolita?
로리타를 찌르는 건 어때?
You have to win love.
사랑을 이겨야 합니다.
Stab Boseok and make him pass out.
보석을 찔러 기절하게 만든다.
Then he can't kiss her.
그러면 그는 그녀에게 키스할 수 없습니다.
If you still act like a pro,
그래도 프로처럼 행동한다면
he'll like you even more.
그 사람은 당신을 더욱 좋아할 거예요.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(극적인 음악 재생)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(음악이 멈춤)
(AUDIENCE MURMURING)
(청중의 불평)
MAN: Hey.
남자: 이봐.
Dohoon.
도훈.
(EXCLAIMS IN SURPRISE)
(놀라서 외친다)
-Hey. -(BOTH LAUGHING)
-안녕하세요. -(둘 다 웃는다)
Long time no see.
오랜만이군요.
I know. It's been ages.
알아요. 오랜 세월이 흘렀습니다.
How have you been?
잘 지내셨나요?
Good. How are you?
좋은. 어떻게 지내세요?
This is crazy.
이건 미친 짓이야.
(LAUGHING)
(웃음)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(경쾌한 음악 재생)
FAMILY: THE UNBREAKABLE BOND
가족: 깨지지 않는 유대
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(음악은 계속됩니다)
DOHOON: She left a will?
도훈: 유언장을 남겼다고?
Mom always liked me more than you.
엄마는 항상 너보다 나를 더 좋아했다.
How can you not remember
어떻게 기억하지 못하나요?
the last word she said?
그녀가 마지막으로 한 말은?
Who'd claim damages on a kids' play?
어린이 놀이에 대해 누가 손해배상을 청구하겠습니까?
Want to come with us?
우리와 함께 가고 싶나요?
DOHOON: Get him in the car. Now.
도훈: 차에 태워주세요. 지금.
CHIEF OH: Find any information on him.
OH 최고: 그에 대한 정보를 찾아보세요.
DOHOON: About that tattoo...
도훈: 그 문신 얘기는..
Who's that guy?
그 사람은 누구입니까?
CHIEF OH: Both then and now,
오 수석: 그때도 그렇고 지금도 그렇고요.
all you care about is yourself.
당신이 관심을 갖는 것은 당신 자신뿐입니다.
Minseo.
민서.
DOHOON: Now I have a reason.
도훈: 이제 이유가 생겼어요.
I have to protect my family.
나는 내 가족을 보호해야합니다.